Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
Matt?
Wake up.
My door, it won't open.
Matt, wake up.
What?
What are you doing?
My door won't open.
Try to get your door open.
Okay, okay.
Okay, hold on.
What're you doing?
Get it going.
I think we're snowed under.
It's just some ice.
If it were just ice, there
would be some visibility,
wouldn't there be?
Well, at least we'll
get the engine going
and it'll help warm us up and,
and loosen the snow.
You're gonna flood it.
There's nothing to flood.
Shit.
Shit!
Okay, don't worry,
don't worry.
Breathe, it's okay.
Got a shot through the back.
Matt.
Shit!
Just don't worry.
Ah shit.
Matt?
Can you just give me
one second, please?
I'm sorry, baby,
I'm just trying to get my
head around this, okay?
I knew we should've
kept on driving.
I knew it, I said it!
Okay, can we calm down, please?
We should've kept on driving
at least another hour or two
to get to a village
or something.
It was freezing rain, in
the middle of the night,
should we have kept going?
We're so fucked.
Can you not be so defeatist?
What're you doing?
Getting my phone.
Come on.
Shit.
The battery is at half life.
Let me see.
Wait.
Come on, come on.
Matt, give me the phone.
Hold on one minute.
Matt, just give me the phone.
Matt!
We need to save the battery.
Can we please not argue?
Okay, I'm sorry.
I just need a few minutes
and I will get us
out of this, okay?
Okay.
Let's see where we are.
What food do we have?
Chicken, cheese, and
a herring sandwich.
Here we go, here we go.
Okay.
All right.
All right, we're on this road
and we're somewhere between
here and here, okay?
Someone is going to pass by.
Can we please not panic?
Hmm.
Okay.
Never know when ice is tight.
What?
Shit.
What's wrong?
My back.
Oh shit.
Okay, you know what?
Come back here.
There's more space.
Come on, come on.
Okay.
You want your legs up here?
Yeah.
How she doing?
She's fine.
She keeps on
kicking, she's okay.
How about you?
Fine, this is, uh,
this is absurd.
Yeah.
What're you doing?
The rental guy said there was a,
there was a roadside kit.
Okay, can we get...
Oh yeah.
Two, three, four.
Here we go.
There we go.
Yay.
And we have light.
Yes.
Now we could clearly see
the shit storm we're in.
No, this is good, it
means we have air.
I'm kidding.
How is that?
It's really good.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Want some?
Shit.
Matt?
I have to pee.
Okay.
Okay, um.
What are you doing?
I got something.
Yeah,
yeah.
Just ball this up and go on it.
You're kidding.
It's what my mother did
when she was bedridden.
I had to keep
changing the towels.
That's disgusting.
You're okay?
Sorry.
I just peed on a towel.
12 days
and only two bottles of water.
That's what we
have to survive on.
What about these,
um, these chocolates?
No, we're not eating those.
That's the only thing
my sister's asked for.
So any ideas how we're getting
out of here with this stuff?
I don't think we
should get out of here.
Matt,
we have to try and get out of
here, we can't just stay here.
I think we should break the
window and use it to dig.
I think that's a
really bad idea.
Why?
Because we don't know
what's out there.
Look, I'm not some kind
of an expert or anything
but I think we should
stay right here.
That's not really
much of a plan.
Okay then try your phone again.
I did, twice.
We're gonna freeze in here.
And you don't think we're
gonna freeze out there?
Come on, at least
we're enclosed.
We've, we've got candlelight,
we have blankets for warmth,
we have body heat.
And what if no one is
out there looking for us?
What if it hasn't even
stopped snowing yet?
If we don't show up
to your book signing...
I can't believe you.
What?
What is so wrong with that?
I can't fucking
believe this.
What's wrong with it
If the weather is as bad
is that you should've,
as you say it is,
or else we wouldn't be
then who's gonna show uC
in this situation at all!
to your book signing anyway?
This is insane.
No, what's insane
is traipsing around
the frozen wilderness,
with a pregnant lady
following the North Star,
hoping we're gonna find a
Fairfield Inn or something.
I just need you
to trust me, okay?
Okay.
Okay then.
We're gonna need more layers.
Okay.
Good morning.
Did you eat?
I'm not even hungry.
What, shit, shit.
What, what is it?
Fuck!
Calm down.
You have to put the cap back on.
I'm sorry, it was an accident.
You just...
I just what?
I just what, Matt?
Nothing.
Great.
Good morning to you.
Sorry, we just need
to be more careful.
Listen.
What?
Hello?
Hey!
We're down here!
In here!
We're here!
Hey!
Ssh.
We in here.
Hello!
Are you okay?
Hey.
Come here.
Nowhere.
Hey.
Ssh, it's okay, okay?
It's gonna be okay.
Okay.
Hello?
Daddy.
Daddy!
Naomi?
Daddy, it's Naomi.
Oh my God, oh my God.
We're stuck.
Is your dad on the phone?
We're in Norway.
Norman?
We're in, we're under some snow
and I don't really
know where we are, dad.
Norman?
Norman we're buried
on the side of a road.
Daddy, can you hear me?
We are 50 miles east
of our hotel.
Can you hear me?
Give me the phone.
Dad.
Give me the...
It's dead.
Why didn't you wake me up?
This was our one chance,
do you know that?
It's getting colder in here.
I know.
We came all this way for
my stupid book signing.
No.
Don't think like that.
Keep your strength up.
You have to eat too.
I'm fine.
What's gonna happen
when the food runs out?
I'm getting close
on this window.
If I can crack it just a few
inches, we could scrape it.
We'll eat the snow.
And eat our way out?
Matthew, we have
to break a window,
we have to start digging.
Do you know what's out there?
Do you know?
Once it's broken, it's broken.
Then what?
Do you remember that story
about that guy from Africa
whose boat capsized?
He survived for weeks
in an air pocket.
No food, nothing.
He stayed put.
You fucking baffle me.
"It'll be fine, sweetheart,
"we'll just pull
right over here,
"we'll drive to the
hotel in the morning."
We both agreed that
it was not a good idea
to drive aimlessly
through the night.
But it was a good idea to
fall asleep during a blizzard!
Did you know we
were gonna wake up
in the middle of the
next fucking Ice Age?
What is your problem?
What are you doing?
What?
Breathe, what's wrong?
What's happening?
Is it the baby?
Naomi?
Pills are in my bag.
We're supposed to be partners.
Just leave it.
Were you ever gonna tell me?
It's not your problem.
We can't be up each
other's asses all the time.
That's being up
each other's asses?
Yes.
People have secrets.
What the fuck does that mean?
Tell me.
What secrets?
Just...
Drop it.
Please.
I think we should
write a letter,
for when we're discovered.
No.
I think we should
consider the possibility.
I don't wanna hear that.
Is that what you've
been so busy writing?
It's not your business.
It is my business.
You don't get to make those
decisions for both of us.
What did you write?
I wrote a stupid story, okay?
About?
A woman in Paris.
Paris.
It's a bit more glamorous
than a giant heap
of snow in Norway.
And?
And she's a helpless
old lady who lives alone
and gets stuck in her bathroom.
Okay?
Go on.
She starts banging on the walls
and clanking on the pipes,
and she even opens her
window and starts yelling,
and nothing.
But the neighbors, they
complain about the noise,
and nothing happens.
Until finally,
when the landlord needs
to collect his rent,
it's when he breaks down
her door and finds her.
Is she alive?
She was barely alive.
Thank you.
But he evicted her.
It is funny, though, who
gets stuck in a bathroom?
Probably the same idiots
who fall asleep
during a blizzard.
Hey!
Help!
Hey, help!
Hey!
Help me!
Help!
Matt, Matt, stop.
Fuck!
It's okay.
No.
Listen, you were
right, you were right.
Vehicles pass by here,
someone else is gonna come.
No one's coming, no
one else will come.
I can't catch a fucking break.
What are you saying right now?
I got fired.
You said you had vacation time.
No.
No, what else can I say, I suck.
I was ashamed, okay?
Fucking shamed, is that
what you need to hear?
What did you want me to say?
Hey, hey look I know the book
isn't off to a great start
and I lost my job,
but great news,
we're gonna have a baby.
Don't turn this around on me.
No.
You're doing this
because you lied.
This isn't about me or the baby.
No, no, no, you never
wanted this baby,
that's why you're still
taking your pills.
Don't you dare!
Don't you fucking dare!
Don't try to tell me how I
feel about having my child!
Then why?
Why are you still
taking your pills?
I brought the pills in
case of an emergency,
what this fucking is!
I'm trying to do
things the right way,
I'm trying to do it everything
the right way, what the fuck!
Except drugging our unborn
child, that's okay, right?
That doesn't cross,
hey, stop it!
Stop it!
Is this what you want, huh?
You want me to lash into you?
Is it?
Get the fuck off me.
Get off me.
What?
Nothing.
Naomi!
What the hell is wrong with you?
Naomi, stop!
Leave me alone!
We're gonna freeze in here,
what the hell is wrong with you?
Stay the fuck away from me!
Oh, God dammit!
What are you doing?
Burning up.
Stop!
I know!
What did you do to me?
Stop it.
No, no, no, stop it, stop it.
Get off of me.
Get off, get off of me!
It's me, it's me.
Get off!
I'm right here.
Let me out!
You can't get out, okay?
I'm not trying to hurt you.
Please, I don't want
you to hurt yourself.
What?
What is it?
Is it the baby?
No?
What is it?
You need to talk to me.
Is this the first
time you felt this?
Why didn't you tell me anything?
I don't know ,
I don't know,
I can't feel anything.
Okay, okay.
I think you're hypothermic,
okay, we need to warm you up.
We need to warm you up, okay?
There you go, there you go.
There you go.
Okay, okay.
Baby,
here, here, here.
There you go.
Come on.
Okay, come on, gotta
put your energy up.
Come on, eat, eat, come on.
Okay.
It's happening,
it's happening again.
I think this is it.
No.
No, no, I can't, I can't
do this now.
I can't.
I don't think we have
much of a choice, baby.
I can't do it, I
can't.
Matt, it's coming.
Okay.
Naomi, you gotta push!
Come on, one more push.
One more push, come on, baby.
Come on.
What is it?
I can't.
Please.
You gotta push, baby.
Push, okay?
Come on.
Pancakes.
Buttermilk pancakes.
With salted butter.
And maple syrup.
And crispy bacon.
Okay.
Oh,
like uh,
applewood smoked
bacon that you just
scoop up some maple syrup.
Waffles.
Belgian waffles.
So crispy and golden with
ever so slightly runny eggs.
Oh, I hate runny eggs.
I love you so much.
I love you.
Babe?
Hmm?
We haven't named her yet.
No, we haven't.
What do you wanna name her?
You make the call.
How about Olivia?
Like your sister?
No.
Like live.
It's perfect.
Hi, Liv.
It's okay, it's okay,
it's okay.
You okay?
Ssh, ssh.
It's okay, it's okay.
It's okay.
You're all right,
come on this way.
I have you.
I got you, I got you.
You're okay.
You're okay, baby.
Give her this.
I'm working up some good heat.
Don't worry about me.
Ssh, ssh, it's okay.
It's okay.
Good morning.
I'm so tired.
Matt.
Can I have some more water?
Babe?
Oh no.
Babe.
Hold on a second.
Baby, wait a minute, it's
okay, baby, it's okay.
Hold on, it's okay, it's
It's okay, babe.
Hey, wait, wait.
Matt?
Hold on, hold on.
Hold on.
This is not.
Three.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
Don't, it's just a letter.
Help me, help me.
Help me.
Come on.
Come on, baby, please, please.
I know.
I know, sweetheart.
It's okay.
Come on, baby, you
have to eat, please.
Please.
Oh, thank God.
Okay.
No, of course not.
She's okay.
She's warm now, thanks to you.
What?
It is tough.
You were never really
looking for your car.
The cabbie was so pissed.
I know.
Let me see you.
Liv,
now.
We're getting out,
Liv, we're getting out.
We're going home, Liv.
It's okay.
It's okay, Liv, it's okay.
At least we're getting out.
We're getting out, Liv.
Babe, thank you.
Goodbye, love.
Stay with me.
Come on, stay with me.
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org